[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What character did Humphrey Bogart portray in the 1951 movie, The African Queen?", "correct_answer": "Charlie Alnutt", "incorrect_answers": ["Charlie Allsworth", "Martin Worth", "Charlie Anderson"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the lead singer of The Max Rebo Band, featured in The Return of the Jedi?", "correct_answer": "Sy Snootles", "incorrect_answers": ["Doda Bodonawieedo", "Max Rebo", "Joh Yowza"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What year did the movie The Breakfast Club come out?", "correct_answer": "1985", "incorrect_answers": ["1981", "1999", "1986"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these is a major problem concerning nutrition value of food, served at restaurants?", "correct_answer": "Oversized meals", "incorrect_answers": ["Foods lacking whole grains and fibers", "Excess protein contents", "Excess sodium contents"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Ambien (zolpidem) is used to treat which one of the following conditions?", "correct_answer": "Insomnia", "incorrect_answers": ["Migraine", "Diabetes", "Peripheral Neuropathy"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What are the colors of the national flag of the Federative Republic of Brazil?", "correct_answer": "White, blue, green and yellow", "incorrect_answers": ["Yellow, green, black and blue", "Red, green and yellow", "Green and black"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does John call Jeremy before they go to the Cleary wedding in the movie Wedding Crashers?", "correct_answer": "Count Chocula", "incorrect_answers": ["Frankenstein", "Captain Hook", "Teddy Bear"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Iridology is a branch of ophthalmology that deals with diseases and treatment of the human iris.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The two reporters who exposed the Watergate scandal were Bernstein and this person.", "correct_answer": "Bob Woodward", "incorrect_answers": ["Dan Rather", "Walter Lippman", "Harry Smith"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Home Alone, Kevins brother had a pet tarantula. What was its name?", "correct_answer": "Axl", "incorrect_answers": ["Sting", "Flea", "Slash"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This scale is used to measure the intensity of a tornado by examining the damage caused by the tornado, when passing over man-made structures.", "correct_answer": "Fujita", "incorrect_answers": ["Mercalli", "Scoville", "Hamilton"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The following group of words (as a whole) makes up a palindrome:\nA man.  A plan.  A canal.  Panama.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]